[{"question": " hey, you&#146;re not going to believe this. i made up a joke and sent it in to playboy. they printed it!", "answer": " i didn&#146;t know playboy prints jokes.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 1, "asentId": 2}, {"question": " yeah, they print jokes, interviews, hard-hitting journalism. it&#146;s not just about the pictures.", "answer": " that didn&#146;t work on mom, it&#146;s not going to work on us.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 3, "asentId": 4}, {"question": " that is funny. it was also funny when i made it up.", "answer": " what?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 7, "asentId": 8}, {"question": " i made that joke up.", "answer": " uh, oh-oh, no you didn&#146;t. i did.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 9, "asentId": 10}, {"question": " yes, i did. i told it to dan at work, and he said it was the funniest joke he&#146;d ever heard.", "answer": " hey, tell dan, &#145;thanks.&#146;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 11, "asentId": 12}, {"question": " what?", "answer": " i&#146;m sorry, i was just reading the joke below it. man, that one is funny.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 13, "asentId": 14}, {"question": " monica, you remember me telling you that joke, right?", "answer": " no.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 15, "asentId": 16}, {"question": " seriously?", "answer": " well, you tell a lot of jokes!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 17, "asentId": 18}, {"question": " look, chandler, it&#146;s my joke. but, hey, if it makes you feel any better they don&#146;t print the name, so it doesn&#146;t really matter who gets credit, right?", "answer": " yeah, i guess.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 19, "asentId": 20}, {"question": "  hey guys.", "answer": "  hey, joey, playboy printed my joke.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 21, "asentId": 22}, {"question": " no, it&#146;s my joke, it&#146;s mine. you can call them, they&#146;ll tell you.", "answer": " it&#146;s my joke.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 23, "asentId": 24}, {"question": " it&#146;s my joke.", "answer": " whoa-whoa-whoa. jokes? you guys know they have naked chicks in there, right?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 25, "asentId": 26}, {"question": " dude, you have got to turn on behind the music. the band heart is having a really tough time, and i think they may break up.", "answer": " let&#146;s go watch it at your place.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 27, "asentId": 28}, {"question": " nah, monica&#146;s watching some cooking show. come on, i don&#146;t want to miss when they were skinny.", "answer": " chandler, chandler, y&#146;know what we should do? you and i should go out and get some new sunglasses.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 29, "asentId": 30}, {"question": " what? no, i want to watch this. . did your cable go out?", "answer": " no, that&#146;s vh-1. i gotta tell you, the music these kids listen to today . . . it&#146;s like a lotta noise to me. i don&#146;t know&#133;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 31, "asentId": 32}, {"question": " joey, why is your cable out?", "answer": " i uh, oh! because, uh, i haven&#146;t really paid the bill", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 33, "asentId": 34}, {"question": " if you need money, will you please-please just let me loan you some money?", "answer": " no, chandler. look, forget about it, okay? look, i know things have been a little tight since janine moved out. oh, was she hot.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 35, "asentId": 36}, {"question": " whoa ho.", "answer": " i know! yeah, but, look i can handle it. all right? look, i can listen to the radio, huh? and ross gave me this great book .", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 37, "asentId": 38}, {"question": "  all right, you want to see if the joke stealer will let us watch the show at his place?", "answer": " sure.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 39, "asentId": 40}, {"question": "  paid your phone bill?", "answer": " not so much.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 41, "asentId": 42}, {"question": "  hey.", "answer": "  it&#146;s only you.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 43, "asentId": 44}, {"question": " wh-wh-what are you doing?", "answer": " we are looking at a playboy.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 45, "asentId": 46}, {"question": " oh, i want to look too! . yikes!", "answer": " so do you think that these pictures&#151;are, are they trying to tell a story?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 47, "asentId": 48}, {"question": " oh, yeah, sure. i mean, like in the case of this young woman, she has lost her clothes, so she rides naked on the horse, she&#146;s crying out, &#145;where are they, where are they?&#146;", "answer": " well, she&#146;s not going to find them lying in the grass like that.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 49, "asentId": 50}, {"question": " oh, yeah. aw, remember the days when you used to go out to the barn, lift up your shirt, and bend over? rachel and monica: yeah.", "answer": " you see, now, i would date this girl. she&#146;s cute, she&#146;s outdoorsy, you know, and she knows how to build a fire. i mean, that&#146;s got to come in handy", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 51, "asentId": 52}, {"question": " okay, i&#146;ve got a question. if you had to pick one of us to date, who would it be?", "answer": "  i don&#146;t know.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 53, "asentId": 54}, {"question": " me neither.", "answer": " rachel.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 55, "asentId": 56}, {"question": " what?!", "answer": " i don&#146;t know.  me neither.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 57, "asentId": 58}, {"question": " you forget how many great songs heart had.", "answer": " yeah.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 59, "asentId": 60}, {"question": " you know, barracuda was the first song i learned to play on the keyboard.", "answer": " so, you heard it, you repeated it, so that must mean you wrote it.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 61, "asentId": 62}, {"question": " oh, you guys, with this joke. i gotta say, i know i cracked up, but i&#146;m not even sure i got it.", "answer": " what, you didn&#146;t get it? the doctor is a monkey.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 63, "asentId": 64}, {"question": "  you are not allowed to laugh at my joke.", "answer": " your joke? well, i think &#145;the hef&#146; would disagree, which is why he sent me a check for one hundred ah-dollars.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 67, "asentId": 68}, {"question": " so, you stole my joke, and you stole my money.", "answer": " well, i was going to stick it in the atm, but now i think i&#146;ll show the sexy teller that i am a published writer.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 69, "asentId": 70}, {"question": " well, she is going to know that you stole the joke.", "answer": " oh, what are you going to do, follow me down there?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 71, "asentId": 72}, {"question": " yeah!", "answer": " well, i&#146;m not going to go now anyway .", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 73, "asentId": 74}, {"question": "  here you go.", "answer": " ah, gunther, i can&#146;t pay for this right now because i&#146;m not working, so i&#146;ve had to cut down on some luxuries like uh, payin&#146; for stuff.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 77, "asentId": 78}, {"question": " well, if you want, you can work here.", "answer": " uh, i don&#146;t know. ya see, it&#146;s just, see i was a regular on a soap opera y&#146;know? and to go from that to this, i just&#133; plus, i&#146;d have to wait on all my friends.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 79, "asentId": 80}, {"question": " okay, but the money&#146;s good, plus you get to stare at rachel as much as you want.", "answer": " what?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 81, "asentId": 82}, {"question": " flexible hours.", "answer": " maybe i could be a waiter. could i use the phone?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 83, "asentId": 84}, {"question": "  she picked rachel. i mean, she tried to back out of it, but it was obvious. she picked rachel.", "answer": "  he took my joke, he took it.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 85, "asentId": 86}, {"question": " it&#146;s wrong. you know what else is wrong? phoebe picking rachel.", "answer": " you know who else picked rachel? ross, and you know what else ross did? he stole my joke. you know what? i&#146;m going to get a joke journal. y&#146;know? and document the date and time of every single one of my jokes.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 87, "asentId": 88}, {"question": " that&#146;s a good idea.", "answer": " yeah!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 89, "asentId": 90}, {"question": " do you know what&#146;s a bad idea?", "answer": " picking rachel.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 91, "asentId": 92}, {"question": " that&#146;s right.  did you hear something?", "answer": " maybe it&#146;s the sound of ross climbing into my brain and stealing my thoughts.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 93, "asentId": 94}, {"question": "  hey, you guys. phoebe and rachel: hey.", "answer": "  oh, don&#146;t you guys look cute. you guys make such a cute couple.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 99, "asentId": 100}, {"question": " monica, what are you doing?", "answer": "  nothing, i&#146;m just trying to recreate some of the fun that we had at my place the other day.  remember, when you picked rachel over me? that was funny.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 101, "asentId": 102}, {"question": " i guess it was kinda funny.", "answer": "  it wasn&#146;t funny at all! why would you do that? why didn&#146;t you pick me?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 103, "asentId": 104}, {"question": " fine. the reason that i was leaning a little bit more toward rachel than you is just that you&#146;re &#133; just &#133; kinda high maintenance&#151;okay let&#146;s go to lunch!", "answer": " that is completely untrue. you think i&#146;m high maintenance? okay, prove it. i want you to make a list and we&#146;re going to go through it point by point!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 105, "asentId": 106}, {"question": " no, okay, you&#146;re right. you&#146;re easy-going. you&#146;re just not as easy-going as rachel. she&#146;s just more flexible and-and mellow. that&#146;s all.", "answer": "  well, people are different.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 107, "asentId": 108}, {"question": " ya, you know, rachel &#133; she&#146;ll do whatever you want. y&#146;know, you can just walk all over her.", "answer": " what? wait a minute. what are you saying, that i&#146;m a pushover? i&#146;m not a pushover.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 109, "asentId": 110}, {"question": " oh, okay,  you&#146;re not a pushover.", "answer": " oh my &#133; you think i&#146;m a pushover. well wait, watch this, you know what? you&#146;re not invited to lunch. what do you think of that? i think that&#146;s pretty strong, that&#146;s what i think. come on, monica, let&#146;s go to lunch.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 111, "asentId": 112}, {"question": " i cannot believe her.", "answer": " i know. where do you wanna go eat?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 115, "asentId": 116}, {"question": " oh, oh, i love that japanese place.", "answer": " i&#146;m sick of japanese. we&#146;re not going there.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 117, "asentId": 118}, {"question": " all right, wherever you wanna go is cool.", "answer": " all right.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 119, "asentId": 120}, {"question": " hey ross, listen, you want anything to drink, &#145;cause i&#146;m heading up there.", "answer": " uh, yeah, i&#146;ll take a coffee. thanks, man.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 125, "asentId": 126}, {"question": " sure.  coffee? &#145;cause i&#146;m going up there.", "answer": " no.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 127, "asentId": 128}, {"question": " no, thank you.", "answer": "  you guys need anything, &#145;cause i&#146;m heading up there.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 129, "asentId": 130}, {"question": " i&#146;d love an ice water.", "answer": " you got it.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 131, "asentId": 132}, {"question": " joey, what are you doing?", "answer": " just being friendly.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 133, "asentId": 134}, {"question": " joey, honey, i don&#146;t think you&#146;re supposed to go back there.", "answer": " nah, it&#146;s okay. right, gunther?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 135, "asentId": 136}, {"question": " don&#146;t wink at me. and put on your apron.", "answer": " okay, but i don&#146;t see you asking any other paying customers to put on aprons.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 137, "asentId": 138}, {"question": " joey, do you work here?", "answer": " no.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 139, "asentId": 140}, {"question": " hey, waiter.", "answer": " yeah? commercial break", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 141, "asentId": 142}, {"question": " joey, what&#146;s going on. what didn&#146;t you tell us you work here?", "answer": " it&#146;s kind of embarrassing, y&#146;know. i mean, i was an actor and now i&#146;m a waiter. it&#146;s supposed to go in the other direction.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 143, "asentId": 144}, {"question": " so is your apron. you&#146;re wearing it like a cape.", "answer": " i mean, the job&#146;s easy and the money&#146;s good, you know? i guess i&#146;m going to be hanging out here anyway. i might as well get paid for it, right? i just feel kind of weird serving you guys.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 145, "asentId": 146}, {"question": " come on, joey, i did it and it was fine.", "answer": " yeah, why would it be weird? hey, joey, can i get some coffee?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 147, "asentId": 148}, {"question": " okay, i guess it doesn&#146;t seem that weird.", "answer": " seriously, i-i asked you before and you still haven&#146;t gotten it.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 149, "asentId": 150}, {"question": " see, now it&#146;s weird again.", "answer": " i think it&#146;s great that you work here. you&#146;re going to make a lot of money, and here&#146;s your first tip: don&#146;t eat yellow snow. . ah ha ha, 2:15, coffeehouse.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 151, "asentId": 152}, {"question": " well, you know what? this is great. finally, i have someone i can pass on my wisdom too. let me tell you about a couple of things i learned while working at the coffeehouse. first of all, the customer is always right.  a smile goes a long way.  and if anyone is ever rude to you? sneeze muffin.", "answer": " thanks, rach. look, you guys are just terrific. y&#146;know? now, how about clearing out of here so i can get some new customers. it&#146;s all about turnover.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 153, "asentId": 154}, {"question": " joey, seriously, can i get my coffee?", "answer": " oh, i&#146;m sorry, ross. i&#146;ll get it for you right now. and since i made you wait, i&#146;ll toss in a free muffin.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 155, "asentId": 156}, {"question": " phoebe. we would like to talk to you for a second.", "answer": " okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 157, "asentId": 158}, {"question": " so, maybe i am a little high maintenance. and maybe rachel is a little bit of a pushover. but you know what we decided you are?", "answer": " yes, we are very sorry to tell you this, but you, phoebe, are flaky.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 159, "asentId": 160}, {"question": " hah!", "answer": " that true, i am flaky.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 161, "asentId": 162}, {"question": " so, what, you&#146;re just, you&#146;re just okay with being flaky?", "answer": " yeah, totally.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 163, "asentId": 164}, {"question": " well, then, i&#146;m okay with being high maintenance.", "answer": " yeah, and i am okay with being a pushover.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 165, "asentId": 166}, {"question": " that&#146;s great. good for you guys.", "answer": " i am not high maintenance!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 167, "asentId": 168}, {"question": " i am not a pushover!", "answer": " who said you were? monica and rachel: you did!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 169, "asentId": 170}, {"question": " hey, gunther. can you uh, can you cover for me? i just got an audition.", "answer": " no, i&#146;m leaving to get my hair dyed.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 173, "asentId": 174}, {"question": " really?! i like your natural color. come on man, it&#146;s a great part. look, check it out. i&#146;m the lead guy&#146;s best friend and i wait for him in this bar and save his seat. listen-listen. &#145;i&#146;m sorry, that seat&#146;s saved.&#146;", "answer": " that&#146;s the whole part?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 175, "asentId": 176}, {"question": " okay, maybe he&#146;s not his best friend, but &#133;", "answer": " okay, i&#146;ll see you in an hour.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 177, "asentId": 178}, {"question": " oh, man, i could totally get that part. &#145;i&#146;m sorry, that seat is taken.&#146;", "answer": " oh, excuse me.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 179, "asentId": 180}, {"question": " no, no, i didn&#146;t mean you. but, you believed me, huh?", "answer": " i believed you were saving this seat for someone.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 181, "asentId": 182}, {"question": " so, you&#146;d hire me, right?", "answer": " for what?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 183, "asentId": 184}, {"question": " exactly! all right, everybody, listen up. the coffeehouse is going to be closed for about an hour.", "answer": " huh? what?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 185, "asentId": 186}, {"question": " it&#146;s my joke.", "answer": " it&#146;s my joke. ross and chandler: it&#146;s my joke.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 189, "asentId": 190}, {"question": " y&#146;know, i don&#146;t think we&#146;re going to settle this.", "answer": " let&#146;s have monica decide.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 191, "asentId": 192}, {"question": " yeah!", "answer": " yeah!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 193, "asentId": 194}, {"question": " hey mon.", "answer": " mon, get out here!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 195, "asentId": 196}, {"question": " okay, okay. you have to help us decide whose joke this is.", "answer": " why do i have to decide?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 199, "asentId": 200}, {"question": " because you&#146;re the only one that can be fair.", "answer": " yeah.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 201, "asentId": 202}, {"question": " i can&#146;t be fair. you&#146;re my boyfriend.", "answer": " yeah, but i&#146;m your brother. we&#146;re family. that&#146;s the most important thing in the world.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 203, "asentId": 204}, {"question": "  don&#146;t try to sway her.   i&#146;m your only chance to have a baby. okay, let&#146;s go.", "answer": " we&#146;ll each tell you how we came up with the joke and then you decide which one of us is telling the truth&#151;me.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 205, "asentId": 206}, {"question": " okay, chandler, you go first.", "answer": " okay, i thought of the joke two months ago at lunch with steve.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 207, "asentId": 208}, {"question": " oh, wait, is he the guy i met at christmas?", "answer": " can i finish my story?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 209, "asentId": 210}, {"question": " do you want me to pick you?!", "answer": " see, i would never snap at you like that.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 211, "asentId": 212}, {"question": " continue.", "answer": " so steve said he had to go to the doctor. and steve&#146;s doctor&#146;s name is doctor muppy. so i said, &#145;doctor monkey?&#146; and that is how the whole doctor monkey thing came up.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 213, "asentId": 214}, {"question": " are you kidding? okay, look. i-i studied evolution. remember, evolution? monkey into man? plus, i&#146;m a doctor, and i had a monkey. i&#146;m doctor monkey!", "answer": " i&#146;m not arguing with that.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 215, "asentId": 216}, {"question": " it&#146;s your joke.", "answer": " is not.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 221, "asentId": 222}, {"question": " hi, chandler. there you are.", "answer": " hi, oh hi.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 223, "asentId": 224}, {"question": "  monica is a self-sufficient, together lady.  being with her has been like being on a vacation. and what may be perceived as high maintenance is merely attention to detail and&#151;&#151;generosity of spirit.", "answer": " wow, you know what? that is the best fake speech i think i&#146;ve ever heard.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 227, "asentId": 228}, {"question": " really? i&#146;ve heard better.", "answer": " wait, wait, he came up with that himself. tell them, chandler.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 229, "asentId": 230}, {"question": "  i&#146;m out of words. should i just say the whole thing again?", "answer": " look, i am not high maintenance. i am not. chandler!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 231, "asentId": 232}, {"question": "  you&#146;re a little high maintenance.", "answer": " ahhh! you are on my list.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 233, "asentId": 234}, {"question": " i&#146;m sorry. you&#146;re not easy-going, but you&#146;re passionate, and that&#146;s good. and when you get upset about the little things, i think that i&#146;m pretty good about making you feel better about that. and that&#146;s good too. so, they can say that you&#146;re high maintenance, but it&#146;s okay, because i like &#133; maintaining you.", "answer": "   i didn&#146;t even tell him to say that. . all right you&#146;re off my list.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 235, "asentId": 236}, {"question": "  phoebe, it&#146;s okay that you don&#146;t want me to be your girlfriend because i have the best boyfriend.", "answer": "  y&#146;know, suddenly i find you very attractive.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 239, "asentId": 240}, {"question": " hey, buddy boy, how&#146;d the audition go?", "answer": " not good, no. i didn&#146;t get the part, and i lost my job here, so &#133;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 241, "asentId": 242}, {"question": " wow! that is a bad audition.", "answer": " how-how did you lose your job here?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 243, "asentId": 244}, {"question": " well, i had the audition but gunther said i had to stay here and be in charge so he could go get his hair dyed. so, i went anyway, and then he fired me.", "answer": " he left work in the middle of the day to do a personal errand and left you in charge when you&#146;ve been working here two days? that&#146;s not, that&#146;s not right.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 245, "asentId": 246}, {"question": " yeah, what are ya gonna do?", "answer": " joey, you can&#146;t let him get away with that. ya know what, i&#146;m not going to let him get away with that. i&#146;m going to say something to him&#151;no, i really shouldn&#146;t say anything&#151;no, i should say something to him.  gunther, i want you to give joey his job back. that is really not fair that you have to fire him&#133;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 247, "asentId": 248}, {"question": " okay.", "answer": " what?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 249, "asentId": 250}, {"question": " he can have his job back.", "answer": " that&#146;s right, he can have his job back. i&#146;m glad we got that all straightened out. there you go, joey, you got your job back.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 251, "asentId": 252}, {"question": " that&#146;s great. thanks rach.", "answer": " yeah, pretty nice, huh? now who&#146;s a pushover?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 253, "asentId": 254}, {"question": "  rach, you&#146;re in my seat.", "answer": " oh, i&#146;m sorry.  ending credits", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 255, "asentId": 256}, {"question": " hey, i never got to hear who you guys would pick to be your girlfriend.", "answer": " i pick you, phoebe.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 257, "asentId": 258}, {"question": " oh, yeah. definitely you, pheebs.", "answer": " yeah, well, i kinda thought.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 259, "asentId": 260}, {"question": " hey.", "answer": " hey. oh, i have a question. if-if-if one of you had to pick one of the other two guys to go out with, who would you pick?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 261, "asentId": 262}, {"question": " no way.", "answer": " i&#146;m not answering that.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep12.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 263, "asentId": 264}]